sakara.com 2019-06-10

# Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Sakara Life

**Terms & Conditions **

Last updated: July 22, 2018

GENERAL

Welcome to the website ("Site") of Sakara Life, Inc (“we”, “us”, “our” or “Sakara”). Please review the following terms that govern your use of and purchase of products from our Site. Please note that your use of our Site constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by these terms (the "Agreement"). If you do not agree to these Terms, you may not access or use the Site or order, receive, or use the meals , products, or content made available through the Site (collectively, the “Products”).

We reserve the right to change or modify these terms at any time and in our sole discretion. Such changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon notice, which may be posted as a modified agreement on the Site with an updated “Last updated” date, or sent out via email. Your use of our Site following any such change constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the terms and conditions as changed. We encourage you to review the Terms frequently to ensure that you understand the terms and conditions that apply when you access or use the Sites or order, receive or use the Products. If you do not agree to the revised Terms, you may not access or use the Sites or order, receive or use the Products.

PRIVACY POLICY

Please refer to our Privacy Policy for information about how we collect, use and disclose information about you. By using our website, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to the Privacy Policy.

NUTRITION AND ALLERGY DISCLAIMER AND LIABILITY WAIVER

We want you to be your healthiest, but we’re not doctors.  You should always consult your doctor before making any changes to your health regime--including starting on a Sakara meal program or using Sakara products.  

By using Sakara products or services, you acknowledge that you are doing so at your own risk, and have consulted with your doctor or other health professional about your diet change.

We do not claim our meal program, products, or services will alleviate, heal or cure any health condition or symptom. The content of this website and any product or service Sakara offers are not meant to diagnose, treat, prevent or cure any medical condition, and should not be used as a substitute for consulting a doctor or other health professional. Any information that you find on this website, on websites we link to, receive from our employees, suppliers, or agents by phone, email or other communication channel, or obtain through contacts you make through Sakara should be verified with your doctor. Consult your doctor with any specific health questions or problems you may have. If you think you have a medical emergency or any condition requiring immediate attention, call your doctor or 911 immediately. The statements made by Sakara Life on this website and our programs and products have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration.

Our program is not intended for people with severe allergies. Our kitchen facilities process and regularly use nuts. We modify meals upon request, but do not provide a product for people with medically-necessitated diets or severe allergies. 

PRICING AND AVAILABILITY

All prices are shown in U.S dollars and applicable taxes and other charges, if any, are additional. We reserve the right to adjust prices as we may determine in our sole discretion, at any time and without notice; provided, however, that if we change the amounts or other charges associated with our various subscription plans, we will provide you with advance notice of such changes. We will not, however, be able to notify you of changes in any applicable taxes. The shipment of your subscription meals or products to you after our delivery of such notice will confirm your acceptance of such changes, unless you cancel your subscription(s) in accordance with the cancellation policies set forth in the “Cancellation of Subscription” section of these terms.

 All of our Products are subject to availability, and we reserve the right to impose quantity limits on any Order, to reject all or part of an Order, to discontinue offering certain Products and to substitute Products (including, but not limited to, specific ingredients in a meal or entire meals) without prior notice. We strive to provide you with high-quality Products, and due to the perishable nature of certain ingredients and market conditions beyond our control, we may be required to make substitutions from time to time. If you are not satisfied with a substitution, please contact us at [info@sakaralife.com](mailto:info@sakaralife.com). Note that gifts with purchase during special programs are available on a first-come, first-serve basis and subject to availability.

Our meal programs are scheduled according to availability. We cannot guarantee that a certain date is available to start the meal program as spots fill up quickly. The cut-off time for the program sign-up is 11:59PM EST two days before you want the program to start (for example: for Monday start, you must order the program no later than 11:59PM EST on preceding Thursday). 

Most Sakara products and services displayed at the Site are available only via online request in the United States while supplies last. Sakara does not ship internationally. In the case of international deliveries via third- party services, Sakara shall not be responsible or be held liable for delivery or use of the products once Sakara has delivered to specified U.S. destination.

PAYMENTS, BILLING AND PROMOTIONS 

Payment is due upon purchasing your Sakara Life product or program. By providing a credit card or other payment method that we accept, you represent and warrant that you are authorized to use the designated payment method and that you authorize us (or our third-party payment processor) to charge your payment method for the total amount of your subscription or other purchase (including any applicable taxes and other charges) (collectively, as applicable, an “Order”). If the payment method cannot be verified, is invalid or is otherwise not acceptable, your Order may be suspended or cancelled. You must resolve any payment method problems before we proceed with your Order. If you want to change or update your payment method information, you can do so at any time by logging into your account. If a payment is not successfully settled and you do not edit your payment method information or cancel your Subscription, you remain responsible for any uncollected amounts and authorize us to continue billing the payment method, as it may be updated. You acknowledge that the amount billed may vary due to promotional offers, preferences you select, changes you make to your Subscription, or changes in applicable taxes or other charges, and you authorize us (or our third party-payment processor) to charge your payment method for the corresponding amount.

By signing up for a meal program subscription, you acknowledge and authorize Sakara to collect, save, and charge your provided payment method for future transactions on your account regarding your subscription. For more details on recurring billing, please see the section titled “CONTINUOUS SUBSCRIPTIONS.”

PROMOTIONS, REFERRALS, AND DISCOUNTS

If you are using a promotion or a discount code, please enter it at checkout to receive an immediate discount. Only one promotion or discount code may be used per order. Promotion or discount codes may be used on already discounted programs, however we reserve the right to cease this practice at any time without notice. If you are using a discount code on a subscription program, once the first week of the subscription ends, we (or our third-party payment processor) will begin billing your designated payment method on a recurring basis for the non-discounted price of your program (plus any applicable taxes and other charges) for as long as your subscription continues, unless you cancel your subscription prior to the cutoff date for any weeks of your program beyond the discounted week. Instructions for cancelling your subscription are described in the “Cancellation of Subscription” section below. Please note that you will not receive a notice from us that the discounted week has ended, or that the full-priced portion of your subscription has begun. Holiday and other special promotions may, at the option of Sakara, carry specific terms and conditions, and we reserve the right to create, amend, and enforce said terms, conditions, and restrictions.

Through our referral program, (Share the Glow program), we offer you the opportunity to receive a $50 discount off of an organic meal delivery program for each new client that you refer to us who completes an order of an organic meal delivery program. We also offer a $50 discount to each new client that you are referring, valid only on their first order of our organic meal delivery program. Please note that in order for you and the new client to be eligible to receive the discount, they must be a new client (have not ordered any meals or products from Sakara Life before), they must purchase an organic meal delivery program, and they must order using the appropriate discount code and **through your shared URL links**. Once they place their eligible order, you will receive an email with a $50 discount credit, valid on our organic meal delivery program.

CONTINUOUS SUBSCRIPTIONS

WHEN YOU REGISTER FOR A MEAL PROGRAM SUBSCRIPTION, YOU EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT (A) SAKARA LIFE (OR OUR THIRD-PARTY PAYMENT PROCESSOR) IS AUTHORIZED TO CHARGE YOU ON A WEEKLY BASIS FOR YOUR MEAL PROGRAM SUBSCRIPTION (IN ADDITION TO ANY APPLICABLE TAXES AND OTHER CHARGES) FOR AS LONG AS YOUR MEAL PROGRAM SUBSCRIPTION CONTINUES, (B) THE AMOUNT YOU ARE CHARGED AND THE NUMBER OF MEALS YOU RECEIVE EACH WEEK MAY VARY DEPENDING ON THE PREFERENCES YOU SELECT, AND (C) YOUR MEAL PROGRAM SUBSCRIPTION IS CONTINUOUS UNTIL YOU CANCEL IT OR WE SUSPEND OR STOP PROVIDING ACCESS TO THE SITES OR PRODUCTS IN ACCORDANCE WITH THESE TERMS. YOU MAY SKIP YOUR WEEKLY MEAL PROGRAM ORDER AS OFTEN AS YOU'D LIKE BY MANAGING YOUR DELIVERY SCHEDULE LOCATED IN YOUR ACCOUNT.

CANCELLATION OF SUBSCRIPTION

YOU MAY CANCEL YOUR MEAL SUBSCRIPTION AT ANY TIME BY LOGGING IN TO YOUR ACCOUNT AND CANCELING SERVICE OR BY EMAILING OUR WELLNESS TEAM, AT INFO@SAKARALIFE.COM. YOU CANNOT CANCEL YOUR FIRST WEEK’S ORDER, AND ALL FUTURE WEEKS MUST BE CANCELED BY 11:59PM ON WEDNESDAY THE WEEK PRIOR TO DELIVERY. YOU WILL BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ALL CHARGES (INCLUDING ANY APPLICABLE TAXES AND OTHER CHARGES) INCURRED WITH RESPECT TO ANY MEAL ORDER PROCESSED PRIOR TO THE CANCELLATION OF YOUR MEAL PROGRAM SUBSCRIPTION.

Orders can be cancelled for a 100% refund up to 7 days prior to the start of your program, with the exception of your first week’s order, which cannot be cancelled. If you need to make changes to your first week, you must email info@sakaralife.com before Wednesday at midnight EST the week prior to request the change.

SHIPPING, HANDLING, AND DELIVERY

You agree to pay any shipping, handling, and delivery charges shown at the time you make a purchase. We reserve the right to increase, decrease, add or eliminate these charges from time to time, but we will provide notice of the charges applicable to you before you make your purchase. Generally, shipping and delivery are handled by a third party courier. When you purchase a meal delivery program or product from Sakara, shipping and delivery times shown on the Sites are estimates only. Actual delivery dates and times may vary. You agree that you will not obtain, or direct shipment of, a product for export.

DELIVERY LOGISTICS

_Current Delivery Area_

We currently deliver to all 48 contiguous states in the U.S.

We ask that you leave detailed delivery instructions in the question box in your cart, e.g.,:

  * Where should we leave your Sakara cooler bag or box? (the more descriptive the better)
  * Is yours a residence or commercial building? 
  * Should we leave at your doorstep, hang on your doorknob, or leave with your doorman?
  * Would you like the delivery team to call you on arrival?

_Delivery Schedule_

We will notify you via email of our should there be a change in delivery schedule due to holidays.

DELIVERY DISCLAIMER

Sakara is not responsible for failed deliveries due to incorrect or incomplete addresses.

All Sakara meals are to be kept refrigerated until consumed and freshness cannot be not guaranteed past the 4th day upon receipt. It is up to the client to maintain freshness once received. Our meals are packaged with insulated liners and ice packs and will typically remain cold and fresh for several hours, but depending on the season and temperature in your geographic area at the time of delivery, advance planning by you should be made for immediate and proper storage of your meals prior to consumption. It’s important to put your Sakara meals and perishable items in the refrigerator when you receive them. By purchasing the Sakara organic meal delivery program, you agree to properly and promptly refrigerate all meals until you plan to eat them.  Since all of our food is fresh (and preservative-free, chemical-free, etc.), it will go bad if not properly taken care of. 

In certain areas, you may be able to provide additional delivery instructions when setting up your account or placing your order, such as requesting that your delivery be left with a doorman or neighbor. Any individual at the delivery address who accepts a delivery from us is presumed to be authorized to receive such delivery. In cases in which you have designated an alternative receiver, such person shall accept the delivery under all of the same terms and conditions that would apply had you accepted the delivery yourself. We will do our best to deliver your meals to you in accordance with your specifications. However, if you are not home to receive the delivery, our team will leave your bag or box according to your delivery instructions or in the safest available spot. Sakara is not responsible for replacing programs once delivered, in the event that you are not home and the delivery is taken.

Once the delivery has been made based on your specifications, we are no longer responsible for any damage or delay on part of other persons, circumstances, or for the security of its contents. You are responsible for inspecting all Products you receive from us for any damage or other issues upon delivery. In addition, you are solely responsible for determining the freshness of the Products you receive. If you think the contents are not suitable for consumption or have been tampered with, please let us know as soon as possible so we can find a more suitable arrangement for the next delivery.

Sakara is not responsible for damage or loss of personal property during deliveries if evidence of misconduct cannot be provided.

PROGRAM AND DELIVERY MODIFICATIONS 

If you are traveling, you can reschedule your deliveries by signing into your account, or email us at [info@sakaralife.com](mailto:info@sakaralife.com) for help. Because all meal programs are made to order, we require that you let us know by Wesnesday at midnight of any changes to be made for programs beginning the following week, including but not limited to paused delivery, address changes, meal modifications, and delivery window changes. 

WEATHER & TRAFFIC ALLOWANCES

Our delivery partners do their best to get your food to you on time so you may enjoy it at its freshest. Still, they run into delays due to weather, traffic and other factors that are outside of their control. We  **cannot**   **guarantee delivery**  within your selected time slot.

In instances of inclement weather, we hold the right to cancel our deliveries in order to avoid putting our delivery teams at risk. In such a case, we will notify you as early as possible and your program will be automatically extended by the number of days cancelled. If this does not suit your schedule, please let us know and we will do our best to find a better arrangement.

As both traffic and weather are outside of Sakara’s normal control, cash refunds cannot be issued for affected orders.

RETURNS, REPLACEMENTS, REFUNDS, AND CREDITS

Since our products are handcrafted and made-to-order with fresh ingredients, we cannot accept returns. All sales are final. If a product arrives damaged or you have concerns, please contact our Wellness Team (info@sakaralife.com). We do our best to ensure a flawless experience, and depending on the circumstances, we may, in our sole discretion, replace the meal or products, provide you with a full or partial refund for the purchase price of that meal or products, or provide you with a credit for that meal or product that will be automatically applied to future deliveries under your meal subscription. If issued, a refund may take 3-5 business days to show up, depending on which bank you use. If you are provided with a credit for a future program, we may implement the credit in a variety of ways at our discretion, including extending the program for you ourselves, providing you with a discount code to use on a future order, or applying a credit to your account, which will be automatically deducted from your next payment. If you have any questions regarding the replacement, refund, and credit logistics, please reach out to us at [info@sakaralife.com](mailto:info@sakaralife.com) for help.

Refunds will not be issued for delays that are the result of factors outside Sakara’s control, including but not limited to weather, traffic, and unexpected events as they relate to our delivery partners. If for any reason have we have to cancel your delivery, you will be notified by email, and the number of meals canceled will be credited to your account which will be applied towards your next subscription payment. If this does not suit your schedule, please let us know and we will do our best to find a better arrangement.

DISCLAIMER

THIS SITE AND ALL CONTENTS OF THE SITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE, BY YOUR USE OF THE SITE, THAT YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND THAT SAKARA SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND RELATED TO YOUR USE OF THIS SITE AND OUR SERVICES.

INDEMNIFICATION

YOU AGREE TO DEFEND, INDEMNIFY AND HOLD SAKARA, ITS EMPLOYEES, OFFICERS, BOARD OF DIRECTORS, CONSULTANTS, AGENTS AND AFFILIATES HARMLESS FROM AND AGAINST ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, DAMAGES, COSTS AND EXPENSES, INCLUDING COSTS AND ATTORNEY’ FEES, ARISING FROM OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND OUR SERVICES.

SITE CONTENTS

Unless otherwise noted, all materials, including images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, video clips, and written and other materials that appear as part of this Site (collectively, the "Contents") are protected by copyrights, trademarks, trade dress and/or other intellectual properties owned, controlled or licensed to Sakara Life Inc. collectively, its subsidiaries and/or affiliates. The Site as a whole is protected by copyright and trade dress, all worldwide rights, titles and interests in and to which are owned by Sakara. Sakara may prosecute infringement to the full extent permitted under applicable law.

The Contents of our Site, and the Site as a whole, are intended solely for personal, noncommercial (other than for the purchase of merchandise from our site) use by the users of our Site. You may download or copy the Contents and other downloadable materials displayed on the Site for your personal use only. No right, title or interest in any downloaded materials or software is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading or copying. You may not reproduce (except as noted above), publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in any sale of, or exploit in any way, in whole or in part, any of the Contents, the Site, or any related software.

USER COMMENTS, FEEDBACK, POSTCARDS AND OTHER SUBMISSIONS

All comments, feedback, postcards, suggestions, ideas, and other submissions disclosed, submitted or offered to Sakara on or by this Site or otherwise disclosed, submitted or offered in connection with your use of this Site (collectively, "Comments") shall be and remain Sakara’s property. Such disclosure, submission or offer of any Comments shall constitute an assignment to Sakara of all worldwide rights, titles and interests in all copyrights and other intellectual properties in the Comments. Thus, Sakara will own exclusively all such rights, titles and interests and shall not be limited in any way in its use, commercial or otherwise, of any Comments. Sakara is and shall be under no obligation (1) to maintain any Comments in confidence; (2) to pay to user any compensation for any Comments; or (3) to respond to any user Comments.

You agree that no Comments submitted by you to the Site will violate any right of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or proprietary right(s). You further agree that no Comments submitted by you to the Site will be or contain, in the sole opinion of Sakara or its representatives, libelous or otherwise unlawful, abusive or obscene material. You are and shall remain solely responsible for the content of any Comments you make.

You agree that Sakara may use and/or disclose information about your demographics and use of the Site in any manner that does not reveal your identity. By participating in Site sweepstakes, contests, promotions, and/or requesting promotional information or product updates, you agree that Sakara may use your information for marketing and promotional purposes.

SAKARA COMMUNICATIONS TO YOU

You agree that Sakara may send electronic mail to you for the purpose of advising you of changes or additions to this Site, about any Sakara products or services, or for such other purpose(s) as Sakara deems appropriate. You have the option to opt-out of marketing communications.

IMAGES

The images and colors displayed on the Site do not necessarily represent or depict actual meal programs or food offered by Sakara. Meals and meal programs are subject to change without notice. 

LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES

To the extent that this Site contains links to outside services and resources, the availability and content of which Sakara does not control, any concerns regarding any such service or resource, or any link thereto, should be directed to the particular outside service or resource. Sakara is not responsible and shall not be held liable for the use of any such content.

INACCURACY DISCLAIMER 

From time to time there may be information on our Site that contains typographical errors, inaccuracies, or omissions that may relate to product descriptions, pricing, and availability. We reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions and to change or update information at any time without prior notice (including after you have submitted your order). 

TERMINATION

This Agreement is effective unless and until terminated by either you or Sakara. Sakara may terminate this Agreement at any time and may do so immediately without notice, and accordingly deny you access to the Site, if in Sakara ' sole discretion you fail to comply with any term or provision of this Agreement. Upon any termination of this Agreement by either you or Sakara, you must promptly destroy all materials downloaded or otherwise obtained from this Site, as well as all copies of such materials, whether made under the terms of this Agreement or otherwise.

## **Privacy Policy**

Last Updated: May 25, 2018

This Privacy Policy describes how information about you is collected, used, and disclosed by Sakara Life, Inc. (here referred to as "we", "us", and "Sakara") in connection with your use of our websites, mobile applications, products, services, communications, or other interactions with us (collectively, the "Service"). Your use of the Service indicates your consent to Sakara's collection, use, and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

Sakara reserves the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in our sole discretion. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will provide notice of such changes, such as by sending an email communication, providing notice through the Service, or updating the “Last Updated” date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you use or access the Service or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

You may contact us regarding this Privacy Policy via email at info@sakaralife.com or write to us at the following address:  
Sakara Life, Attn: Data Privacy Manager  
580 Broadway, Suite 210  
New York, NY 10012

**Collection of information:** We may collect information about you in connection with your use of the Service, including information you transit to or through the Service. We collect both information you provide directly to us (for example, your account and transaction information) and information that is automatically collected when you use or access the Service (for example, your IP address and mobile device information). The types of information we collect about you include:

a.) Information You Provide to Us, for example when you register for a Sakara account, purchase a product, sign up for a subscription, subscribe to a newsletter or email list, participate in a survey, contest, promotion, or event, apply for a job, communicate with us via email or third party platforms, request client support, or other methods of communication with us

  1. Account information, such as your name, email address, password, postal address, phone number, subscription, delivery and dietary preferences, and any other information you choose to provide
  2. Transaction information, such as information about Sakara products or services that you purchase, shipping and delivery information and any information related to refunds, credits, and cancellations. We may also collect and store limited payment information from you, such as payment card type and expiration date and the last four digits of your payment card number; however, we do not collect or store full payment card numbers and all transactions are processed by our third party payment processor.
  3. Information about others, such as the names and email addresses of gift recipients when you purchase gifts through the Service, send a product to a recipient other than yourself, or invite friends or family to Sakara
  4. Other information you choose to provide, such as when you participate in a survey, contest, or promotion, when you interact with or mention us on third party social media sites, or when you request technical or customer support

b.) Information we Collect Automatically, for example when you access or use the Service

  1. Log Information: When you visit the Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information, such as your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, operating system, browser type and language, referring URLs, access times, pages viewed, links clicked and other information about your interactions with the Services
  2. Mobile Device Information: We collect information about the mobile device you use to access or use the Service, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information.
  3. Activity information: We may store information about your use of the Service, such as website pages visited, date and time of your visit, transactions you initiate, and emails you receive, open, and click
  4. Information collected by cookies and other tracking technologies: We and our service providers use various tracking technologies, including cookies, web beacons, tags, scripts, local shared objects such as HTML5 and Flash (sometimes called "flash cookies"), advertising identifiers (including mobile identifiers such as Apple's IDFA or Google's Advertising ID) and similar technology (collectively, "Cookies") to collect information about you in connection with your use of the Service. Cookies may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may collect and transmit information about you and your use of the Service, such as your browser type, search preferences, IP address, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session. you interact with the Service, including information about your browsing and purchasing behavior. For more information about cookies and how to manage your cookie preferences, please see the Your Choices section below.

Unless otherwise specified, we will retain the information described here indefinitely. Please see the Your Choices section below for more information on your choices related to how we store your information. 

**Use of Information:** We may use the information we collect about you for a variety of purposes, including to:

  1. Provide, maintain, and improve the Service and products provided by Sakara
  2. Manage your account and send you related information, including confirmations, updates, technical notices, security alerts and support and administrative messages
  3. Respond to your comments, questions, and requests, and provide customer service
  4. Communicate with you about the Service, products, offers, surveys, events, content, and other news and information we think may be of interest to you. When you sign up for an account or use certain features of our Service, you are opting to receive messages from us. For more information about how to manage your communication preferences, please see the Your Choices section below
  5. Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with the Service and our communications to you
  6. Detect, investigate, and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities, protect the rights and property of Sakara and others, and comply with legal requirements
  7. Personalize and improve the Service and provide advertisements, content, and features that match your profile and interests, and remember information about your preferences for the Service
  8. Facilitate contests, sweepstakes, and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards
  9. Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected 

**Sharing of information:** We respect your privacy online. We do not sell or rent your information to third parties unless explicitly specified. However, we may share the personal information we do collect about you with third parties as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy

  1. With vendors, consultants, and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work or perform services on our behalf, such as fulfill your order or assist in communication with you
  2. When you interact with us on third party social media sites, information that you provide may be displayed publicly, such as your name, photos, and other information you choose to provide
  3. When you purchase a product that includes benefits from a partner organization, your email address may be shared with the partner for the purposes of fulfilling your purchase. Please refer to partner companies' sites for their Privacy Policy regarding the collection, use, and storage of your personal information
  4. In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, rule, regulation or legal process
  5. If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our Terms & Conditions or other policies, to protect the rights, property or safety of Sakara and others
  6. In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, acquisition, sale of assets or any business, other change of control transaction or financing; between any future parent, subsidiary, and/or affiliated company
  7. With advertising and analytics partners to serve advertisements on our behalf across the internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use Cookies in the same way we do, to among other things, track and analyze data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests and better understand your online activity. For more information about how to manage having your web browsing information used for advertising purposed, please see the Your Choices section below
  8. With your explicit consent or at your direction
  9. Links: Our website may contain links to third party services, like another business's URL. Except as described here, we do not share your personal information with them and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on or applicable to all such third party services

We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you 

**Security** : Sakara takes reasonable measures and use various safeguards to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to or from us over the Internet. In particular, email sent to or from Sakara may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. 

**Your Choices**

  1. Account Information: You may update, correct, or modify information about you at any time by logging into your account or emailing us at info@sakaralife.com. If you wish to deactivate your account, please email us at info@sakaralife.com, but note that we may continue to retain information about you for the purposes authorized under this Privacy Policy unless prohibited by law.
  2. Cookies: Most web browsers are set to accept Cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. The method for disabling Cookies may vary by device and browser, but can usually be found in your device or browser preferences or security settings. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Service.
  3. Online advertising networks: As you browse our website, online ad
  4. Promotional Communications: You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by following the instructions in those communications or by emailing us at info@sakaralife.com. If you choose to opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account or our ongoing business relations

**Children** : Use of Sakara's website and Sakara accounts is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us at info@sakaralife.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account

**California Residents - Your California Privacy Rights** : We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose of directly marketing their goods or services to you. If you have any questions regarding this policy, or would like to change your preferences, you may contact us at the address listed above.
